voyeur-house.tv 2019-03-30

# Privacy policy of VH TV

This Privacy Policy applies to the following websites: voyeur-house.tv (individually, a “Site”).

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

**Information Collection and Use**

We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points throughout our Site.

**Registration and Order Forms**

In order to gain access to our Site, you may be requested to provide us with your date of birth. In addition, in order to purchase goods and services from our Site, or to become a member of our Site, a user must complete the on-line registration/order form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include name, e-mail address and etc.). If we have trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie terminates (depends of your browser's settings). For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, we are able track IP addresses and browser preferences in order to enhance and personalize your experience at our Site.

**Profiling**

From time to time, we may combine personal information and preferences collected on-line with personal information and preferences collected off-line in order to enhance and personalize our services.

**Law Enforcement**

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child pornography.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security**

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to [contact us](https://voyeur-house.tv/support) if you are interested in learning more about our security measures.

**Third Party Sources of Information**

From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive from you with information we obtain from third party sources.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as e-mail address), or if a user no longer desires our service, you may [contact us](http://voyeur-house.tv/support) to correct or update this information. **Choice/Opt-out**

From time to time, we may send our users e-mail or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us.

**Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use any of our Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use any of our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice).

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to [contact us](http://voyeur-house.tv/support) regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your user name so we can service you quicker.

For voyeur-house.tv and its related sites, please [contact us](https://voyeur-house.tv/support).
